Do you know what's more sophisticated?
This bro arrives by cross.
My Chevette doesn't even know when he's going back from cleaning up.
And this is the partner's car.
I don't even have a cap to get into that place.
Now here at titania,
leaving the brownie tea to the crowd,
right?
My first know the product.
That this brother?
Be interesting not be interested is it on?
What's the okay?
Haha?
How do you behave like that?
Like inside the office to be like a nurse.
I'm kind of lost bro has to have hair has to have hair saw
that I promised next video I take off the cap guys
bro?
The guys even have a movie theater here.
Imagine you sit here.
View 1 presentation 1 anesthetized film even drew from this stop
It is fine?
Cool here brother.
This scenario here is the Universe called the red dome here.
Doidão was a famous guest today I am the founder of Brown do Zé PC pleasure.
How is Charlie Brown doing?
Tell us 1 little bit.
How did you get the idea for Charlie Brown?
It started with R$1,
right?
Hand
Sasa.